<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://pranshubheda.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://pranshubheda.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2023-12-29T20:24:49+00:00</updated><id>https://pranshubheda.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Pranshu’s Blog</title><subtitle>A simple, whitespace theme for academics. Based on [*folio](https://github.com/bogoli/-folio) design. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">2023 Wrap up</title><link href="https://pranshubheda.github.io/blog/2023/EOY-2023/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="2023 Wrap up"/><published>2023-12-29T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-12-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pranshubheda.github.io/blog/2023/EOY-2023</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pranshubheda.github.io/blog/2023/EOY-2023/"><![CDATA[<h1 id="2023-a-rollercoaster-of-wins-and-wisdom-">2023: A Rollercoaster of Wins and Wisdom! 🚀</h1> <p><img src="https://media.giphy.com/media/xUySTQZfdpSkIIg88M/giphy.gif" alt=""/></p> <h2 id="personal-wins">Personal Wins</h2> <h3 id="from-code-to-cardio">From Code to Cardio</h3> <p>2023, you wild thing! Here are some victories that had me fist-pumping:</p> <ul> <li><strong>Promotion Party:</strong> Got that senior software engineer title! Cue the confetti.</li> <li><strong>Morning Gym Vibes:</strong> Woke up and actually went to the gym regularly. Who am I?!</li> <li><strong>Love &amp; Chill:</strong> Leveled up my relationship game, and my partner and I feel much more comfortable.</li> <li><strong>Me Time Travel:</strong> Discovered more about myself through adventures with my partner.</li> <li><strong>House Party:</strong> Bought a new house. 🏠</li> </ul> <h3 id="goals-crushed-em">Goals? Crushed ‘Em!</h3> <p>Did I set goals? Heck yeah!</p> <ul> <li><strong>Gym Grind:</strong> Crushed the workout goals. Next December, expect a superhero physique.</li> <li><strong>Home Sweet Home:</strong> Bought a house for my family.</li> <li><strong>Personal Growth Saga:</strong> Unlocked hidden levels in personal growth and relationship.</li> </ul> <h2 id="career-quests">Career Quests</h2> <h3 id="phd-drama-and-confidence-boost">PhD Drama and Confidence Boost</h3> <p>Work-wise, it was a ride too:</p> <ul> <li><strong>PhD Pondering:</strong> Thought about a PhD in machine learning. Did all the prep, even wrote the SOP. Never hit send. Oops!</li> <li><strong>Promo Confidence:</strong> Got promoted and now solving problems more confidently.</li> <li><strong>Mentor Magic:</strong> Feels good to give back. I had really good menors while I was coming up in my career. You get what you give.</li> </ul> <h2 id="global-plot-twists">Global Plot Twists</h2> <p>The world threw curveballs, and I caught ‘em:</p> <ul> <li><strong>Hamas Drama:</strong> Israel got me thinking about life’s unpredictability.</li> <li><strong>Stock Market Wisdom:</strong> Sold stocks too early, learned to commit to decisions. Talk is cheap; actions speak louder!</li> </ul> <h2 id="tech-tales">Tech Tales</h2> <p>Geeked out on cool tech stuff:</p> <ul> <li><strong>Transformer Awesomeness:</strong> Deep learning transformers became my jam.</li> <li><strong>Fusion Fascination:</strong> Explored nuclear fusion and superconducting materials. Nerd level: Expert.</li> </ul> <h2 id="personal-growth-party">Personal Growth Party</h2> <p>Leveling up, one day at a time:</p> <ul> <li><strong>Workout Fiesta:</strong> Hit the gym, listened to killer music, and read awesome books. Positive vibes only!</li> <li><strong>Wanderlust Love:</strong> Fell in love with travel and socializing. Life’s a party; I’m just living in the moment.</li> </ul> <h2 id="epic-moments">Epic Moments</h2> <ul> <li><strong>House Hunt Victory:</strong> Offer accepted! Cue the happy dance.</li> <li><strong>PTO Surprise Call:</strong> Manager called on PTO with good news. Usually bad news, right? Not this time!</li> </ul> <h2 id="challenges--wisdom">Challenges &amp; Wisdom</h2> <p>Life lessons in 2023:</p> <ul> <li><strong>Individual Odyssey:</strong> You control you. Others sail their own ships. Be a good example.</li> <li><strong>Role Model Realization:</strong> Talk is cheap; actions speak volumes.</li> </ul> <h2 id="pop-culture-picks">Pop Culture Picks</h2> <p>Fun stuff that rocked my world:</p> <ul> <li><strong>Movie Magic:</strong> “Next Goal Wins” was a blast. Living in the present—lesson learned!</li> <li><strong>Concert Vibes:</strong> Travis Scott concert with my cousin? Epic.</li> </ul> <h2 id="squad-and-seva">Squad and Seva</h2> <p>Building bonds and giving back:</p> <ul> <li><strong>Family Power:</strong> Lucky to have a supporting family.</li> <li><strong>Seva Star:</strong> Regular community service—doing my bit.</li> </ul> <h2 id="resolutions-reality-check">Resolutions Reality Check</h2> <p>Checking in on those New Year promises:</p> <ul> <li><strong>Glow-Up Journey:</strong> Progressed in the personality glow-up. Gym gains? On the way!</li> <li><strong>Startup Dreams:</strong> Stealth mode activated. Two startups in the making.</li> </ul> <h2 id="2024-game-plan">2024 Game Plan</h2> <p>Bringing the hype to the new year:</p> <ul> <li><strong>Gym Warrior:</strong> Keep crushing it at the gym, spill thoughts into my journal.</li> <li><strong>Startup Shuffle:</strong> Dive deep into those stealth startups. Monthly blog posts—coming at ya!</li> <li><strong>Love Story:</strong> Keep the partner vibes strong. 👩‍❤️‍👨</li> </ul> <p>As I bid adieu to 2023, I’m carrying the lessons, victories, and good vibes into the next chapter. 2024, let’s do this! 🚀</p> <p><img src="https://media.giphy.com/media/3o7qDSOvfaCO9b3MlO/giphy.gif" alt=""/></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="yearly-wrap-up"/><category term="fun"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking back on the year 2023]]></summary></entry></feed>